Society for Canadian Women in Science and Technology fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Projects, programs and events files, 1981 - 2004; F-39-5; Analog originals: 1.74 m of textual records 13 photographs 19 sound recordings (25 audio cassettes) 1 multiple media record (1 optical disk - CD)
  - Events and projects files, 1981 - 2004; F-39-5-1; 46 cm of textual records 1 sound recording; Physical description: series includes 1 audio cassette.
    Sub-series comprises records relating to SCWIST-organized events and projects. Activities documented include the founding of the BC chapter of the Canadian Association for Girls in Science (CAGIS); the organization of educational conferences and workshops (Discover the Possibilities, High School Outreach pilot project, Quantum Leaps in conjunction with Douglas College, Say Yes to Math and Science Careers for Women, Science for Young Canadians, Visiting Scientists Project, Women Do Math conferences, and the Women Inventors Project); the production of professional and educational resource material (the Registry of Skilled Women, BC and Yukon, the video What Do Scientists Do?); and the organization of information and networking events for professionals in the fields of science and technology (Speakers' Bureau, Small Business Women's Workshops, Women in Science panels, XX Evenings at Science World). Records consist of correspondence; reports; grant applications and supporting documentation; presentations; audio recordings; handbooks and manuals; event evaluations; publicity brochures, and contracts.
    - Canadian Association for Girls in Science (CAGIS), 1996 - 1998; F-39-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Canadian Association for Girls in Science (CAGIS), 1997 - 1998; F-39-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Canadian Association for Girls in Science (CAGIS), 1997; F-39-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Chilliwack Career Fair, 1992 - 1994; F-39-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Discover the Possibilities conference, 1992 - 1995; F-39-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Events, 1982 - 1991; F-39-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Events - planning, 1988 - 1992; F-39-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Grant applications - general, 1982 - 1991; F-39-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Grant applications - general, 1994 - 1995; F-39-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - High School outreach pilot project, 1984; F-39-5-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Quantum Leaps, 1993 - 1995; F-39-5-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Registry of Skilled Women - BC and Yukon, 1981 - 1985; F-39-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Say Yes to Math and Science careers for women, 1987 - 1988; F-39-5-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Science and Technology week, 1993 - 1997; F-39-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Science for young Canadians, 1984; F-39-5-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Small business women's workshops, 1995 - 1996; F-39-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Speaker's bureau, 1992 - 1993; F-39-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 39-6)
    - Visiting scientists project, 1987 - 1989; F-39-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - What Do Scientists Do? (video), 1990 - 1992; F-39-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - What Do Scientists Do? (video royalties), 1991 - 1994; F-39-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Women Do Math conferences, 1987 - 1991; F-39-5-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Women in Math / Science conference, 1982; F-39-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Women in Science panel, 1982; F-39-5-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
      - SCWIST Panel: The Vanishing Act, 1982; F-39-5-1-0-23-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3082)
        Jane Hutton; Marg Wolff; Haggerty, Sharon; Nina Fisher; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item5.
    - Women Inventors project, 1992 - 1993; F-39-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Scientific Attitudes Questionniare, 1984; F-39-5-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Women scientists and part time work, 1982; F-39-5-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Elementary science - general, 1986; F-39-5-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Science education in BC for girls, 1988; F-39-5-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - What do scientists do?, 1989 - 1991; F-39-5-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Shad Valley, 1989 - 1992; F-39-5-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Science teaching in schools, 1990 - 1991; F-39-5-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Women at frontier of excellence, 1994; F-39-5-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Career choice survey - science promotion programs, 1994 - 1995; F-39-5-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Career choice survey - science promotion programs, 1995 - 1996; F-39-5-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Cwest, 1995; F-39-5-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Turn your child onto math, science, 1995; F-39-5-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Women entrepreneurs conference, 1996; F-39-5-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Women in science-based businesses, 1996; F-39-5-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Grant - science and technology week, 1998; F-39-5-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Grant - science and technology week, 1999; F-39-5-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 39-20)
    - Grant application - Motorola, 1998 - 2000; F-39-5-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Grant applications - general, 1999; F-39-5-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Wearing the face of change, 1999; F-39-5-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Women in high tech fields, 1999; F-39-5-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Immigrating women in science, 1999 - 2003; F-39-5-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Quantum leaps conference, 1999 - 2004; F-39-5-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Quantum leaps conference, 2001; F-39-5-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Where are the women? WISSTE study, 1997 - 1998; F-39-5-1-0-48 (Archival box - small 39-22)
    - Where are the women? WISSTE study, 1998 - 1999; F-39-5-1-0-49 (Archival box - small 39-22)
    - Where are the women? WISSTE study, 1999; F-39-5-1-0-50 (Archival box - small 39-22)
  - First National Conference on Women in Science and Technology files, 1982 - 1984; F-39-5-2; 10 cm of textual records 18 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 18 sound recordings on 24 audio cassettes (originals).
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the organization of the first National Conference on Women in Science and Technology, held in Vancouver BC in May 1983. Activities documented include conference planning, funding, publicity, presentations and evaluations. Records consist of correspondence; reports; grant applications and supporting documentation; publicity brochures, programs and press releases; presentations, audio recordings, transcripts and published conference proceedings; and conference evaluation forms and summaries.
    - Brochures and flyers, 1983; F-39-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-39-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Equals workshop, 1983; F-39-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Evaluation, 1983; F-39-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Funding, 1983 - 1984; F-39-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 39-7)
    - Proceedings (copy 1), 1983; F-39-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Proceedings (copy 2), 1983; F-39-5-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Program and speakers, 1983; F-39-5-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Public relations, 1982 - 1983; F-39-5-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Tapes - index and transcripts, 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
      - Keynote address. Dr Rose Sheinin (University of Toronto): Women in Science ... and Why Not/Nought?, 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3083)
        Rose Sheinin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item6. Creator's original file classification code: T-1.
      - Panel: Science, Women, Grants and Sports. Janet Ferguson, 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3084)
        Janet Ferguson; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item18. Creator's original file classification code: T-2.
      - Lucie Pepin: Expanding your Horizons, 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3085)
        Lucie Pepin; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item19. Creator's original file classification code: T-3.
      - Panel: Careers on the Go., 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3086)
        Marilyn Berugian; Fiona Esen; Louise Bell; Judith Miller; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item20. Creator's original file classification code: T-3.
      - Panel: Women Scientists, 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3087, Audio cassette OBJ-3088)
        Edith Camm; Dormer Ellis; Lasvergnas-Gremy, J.; Benston, Maggie; Joanne Hannah; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item21, F-39-item22. Creator's original file classification code: T-4.
      - Barbara Smail (University of Manchester): "Yes" to the GIST Program – Affirmative Action Encouraging Girls into Science and Technology, 20 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3089, Audio cassette OBJ-3090)
        Smail, Barbara; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item23, F-39-item24. Creator's original file classification code: T-5.
      - Panel: Doorways to Science Education, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3091, Audio cassette OBJ-3092)
        Gaalen Erickson; Heidi Kass; Haggerty, Sharon; Joan Scott; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item25, F-39-item26. Creator's original file classification code: T-6.
      - Panel: Women in Universities and Colleges – Statistics, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3093)
        Janet Stein; Palmer, Evelyn T.; Judy Einstein; Moon, Barbara; Maryke Gilmour; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item27. Creator's original file classification code: T-7.
      - Panel: Re-entry to the Workforce, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3094)
        EQUALS Group (Berkeley); Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item28. Creator's original file classification code: T-8.
      - Panel: Juggling Home, Family and the Scientific Career, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3095)
        LeCouteur, Penny; Helga Guderly; Margaret Henry; Marilyn Berugian; Myers, Judy; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item29. Creator's original file classification code: T-9.
      - Linda Steingarten: The Paucity of Patents Granted to Women, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3096)
        Linda Steingarten; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item7. Creator's original file classification code: T-10.
      - Workshop: EQUALS in Technology – The EQUALS Group, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3097)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item8. Creator's original file classification code: T-11.
      - Evelyn Fox Keller: Is Science Male?, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3098)
        Keller, Evelyn Fox; Lowe, Marian; Benston, Maggie; Hubbard, Ruth; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item9. Creator's original file classification code: T-12.
      - Workshop: Stategies to Encourage Girls into Science – Bill McNulty, 21 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3099)
        McNulty, Bill; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item10,. Creator's original file classification code: T-13.
      - Workshop: Entering the Scientific Workforce – Pam Biela, 22 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3100, Audio cassette OBJ-3101)
        Pam Biela; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item11, F-39-item12,. Creator's original file classification code: T-14.
      - Donna Brown (CAWIS): The Future of Canadian Women in Science, 22 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3102)
        Donna Brown; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item14. Creator's original file classification code: T-15.
      - Open Forum: Social Issues in Science, 22 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3103, Audio cassette OBJ-3104, Audio cassette OBJ-3105)
        Penny Francoeur; Savan, Beth; Elaine Bernard; Hubbard, Ruth; Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item13, F-39-item15, F-39-item16. Creator's original file classification code: T-16.
      - Concluding Remarks: Hilda Ching, 22 May 1983; F-39-5-2-0-10-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3106)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-39-item17. Creator's original file classification code: T-17.
  - Girls in Science program files, 1984 - 1990; F-39-5-3; 32 cm of textual records 5 photographs; Physical description: 5 photographs located in F-39-5-3-28
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the development and delivery of the Girls in Science program, designed to encourage girls to consider science and technology careers. Girls in Science began in 1984 as a series of week-long summer workshops offered by SCWIST throughout British Columbia for girls aged 9 to 12, featuring a range of hands-on activities. In 1988 the direct management of the workshops passed from SCWIST to the local communities, who organize them on the basis of the SCWIST manual, Imagine the Possibilities. Records consist of correspondence, memoranda and reports; grant applications and supporting documentation; workshop presentations and overheads; teaching activities material; evaluations; handbooks and manuals (including annotated drafts and the first and second editions of Imagine the Possibilities); photographs; publicity brochures; and press clippings.
    - Action Plan - correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-39-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Action Plan - report and presentations, 1984; F-39-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Undated workshop activities 1/3, [ca 1984]; F-39-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Undated workshop activities 2/3, [ca 1984]; F-39-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - Undated workshop activities 3/3, [ca 1984]; F-39-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - 1984 workshops - activities, F-39-5-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - 1984 workshops - publicity, 1984 - 1985; F-39-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 39-8)
    - 1984 workshops - reports, F-39-5-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1985 workshops - activities 1/2, 1985 - 1986; F-39-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1985 workshops - activities 2/2, 1985 - 1986; F-39-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1985 workshops - forms, F-39-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1985 workshops - publicity, F-39-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1985 workshops - reports, F-39-5-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1986 workshops - activities, F-39-5-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1986 workshops - extra activities, F-39-5-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1986 workshops - publicity, F-39-5-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1986 workshops - reports, 1986 - 1987; F-39-5-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1987 workshops - activities, F-39-5-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1987 workshops - correspondence, F-39-5-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1987 workshops - forms, F-39-5-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1987 workshops - publicity, F-39-5-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1987 workshops - reports, F-39-5-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - activities 1/2, F-39-5-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - activities 2/2, F-39-5-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - correspondence, F-39-5-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - forms, F-39-5-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - overheads, F-39-5-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
    - 1988 workshops - photographs, F-39-5-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 39-9)
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - 1988 workshops - publicity, F-39-5-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - 1988 workshops - reports, 1988 - 1989; F-39-5-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Correspondence - Revenue Canada, 1988 - 1989; F-39-5-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Grants and applications, 1984; F-39-5-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Grants and applications, 1984 - 1985; F-39-5-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Grants and applications, 1987; F-39-5-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Grants and applications, 1988 - 1989; F-39-5-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - 1st edition, 1989; F-39-5-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - 2nd revised edition, 1990; F-39-5-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - instructors' comments, 1989; F-39-5-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - BCIT office, 1989; F-39-5-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - requests, 1988 - 1990; F-39-5-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Imagine the Possibilities - forms, 1988 - 1989; F-39-5-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Proposal, 1987 - 1988; F-39-5-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
    - Report, 1984; F-39-5-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 39-10)
  - Elementary Science Workshop program files, 1985 - 1989; F-39-5-4; 12 cm of textual records 6 photographs; Physical description: 6 photographs located in F-39-5-4-8
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the development and delivery of the Elementary Science Workshops, a program designed to improve science instruction by elementary school teachers. Sessions for local teachers were held in the community by a Resource Person while the workshops as a whole were overseen by a Project Coordinator, assisted by a SCWIST program committee. Records consist of correspondence; reports; committee meeting minutes and supporting papers; grant applications and supporting documentation; workshop presentation materials; photographs; and publicity brochures.
    - Correspondence, 1985 - 1989; F-39-5-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Grants and applications, 1985 - 1987; F-39-5-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Grants and applications, 1986; F-39-5-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Grants and applications, 1987 - 1988; F-39-5-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Publicity, 1987; F-39-5-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Reports, 1985 - 1988; F-39-5-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Workshops, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Workshops - photographs, [198-?]; F-39-5-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Program binder, vol. 1, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Program binder, vol. 2, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Program binder, vol. 3, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Program binder, vol. 4, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Program binder, vol. 5, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
    - Program binder, vol. 6, 1988; F-39-5-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 39-21)
  - Project Tomorrow program files, 1992 - 1999; F-39-5-5; 24 cm of textual records 2 photographs; Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-39-5-5-3
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the development and delivery of the Project Tomorrow program. Project Tomorrow was initiated in 1992 as a series of seminars offered by SCWIST for parents, parent advisory committees and elementary school teachers designed to help them encourage and sustain the interest of girls in science and technology. Records consist of correspondence; reports; committee meeting minutes and supporting papers; grant applications and supporting documentation; presentation materials, transparencies and overheads; schedules and evaluations; contracts; handbooks and manuals; and publicity brochures.
    - Committee meeting minutes, 1992 - 1995; F-39-5-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Community Interaction Days - planning, 1995; F-39-5-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Community Interaction Days - Kamloops, 1995; F-39-5-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Community Interaction Days - Burnaby, 1995; F-39-5-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Community reports, 1995; F-39-5-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Employee contracts, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - General, 1997 - 1998; F-39-5-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Grants and applications, 1993; F-39-5-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 39-11)
    - Grants and applications, 1994; F-39-5-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Grants and applications, 1995; F-39-5-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Grants and applications, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Kamloops Career Fair, 1994; F-39-5-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Manuals - Outreach coordinator, 1994; F-39-5-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Pamphlets - Wonder series, 1993 - 1994; F-39-5-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Presentation material, 1993; F-39-5-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Presentation material, 1993 - 1994; F-39-5-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Presentation material, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Publicity - annual school mail out, 1997 - 1998; F-39-5-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speaker requests, 1992 - 1994; F-39-5-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speaker requests, 1997 - 1999; F-39-5-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speaker schedules, 1997 - 1999; F-39-5-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speaker updates, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speaker workshops, 1993 - 1996; F-39-5-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Speakers - books, educators, Science and Technology (Best) conference, 1994; F-39-5-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Workshop evaluations - summaries, 1993 - 1996; F-39-5-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Workshop evaluations, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - Workshop evaluations, 1998; F-39-5-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 39-12)
    - General, 1994 - 1999; F-39-5-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 39-23)
    - Final reports, 1995 - 1996; F-39-5-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 39-23)
    - Community science, math and technology days, 1996; F-39-5-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 39-23)
    - Committee meeting minutes, 1997 - 1999; F-39-5-5-0-31 (Archival box - standard 39-23)
  - Work Pathfinder program files, 1994 - 1999; F-39-5-6; 12 cm of textual records 1 multiple media record; Physical description: sub-series includes 1 CD.